# **DEVENYE DUNN**

**BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER** 



5615 Sundial Dr, Jacksonville, FL, US

## Contact **Follow** +1 (202) 854-8584 https://x.com/Devenye10 devedunn4947@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/devenye

#### SUMMARY

High-skilled blockchain engineer with hands-on experience in building System program, NFT, writing smart contracts and dApps. I've worked on 50+ projects and complex business problems in various industries including markets, healthcare, real estate, eCommerce and insurance. Creative and passionate, self-learning who had rich experience in blockchain developing.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Blockchain Lead Engineer**

Microsoft / September 2023 to February 2024

https://devenye.github.io/devenye/

- Engineered a proprietary blockchain solution for a supply chain management system of \$MSFT(MICROSOFT COIN), increasing traceability and reducing counterfeit incidents, which directly contributed to the growth in client trust and business volume.
- Led a team of developers in the successful migration of a traditional loyalty points system to a new blockchain platform, doubling redemption rates and increasing partner participation.
- Implemented smart contract audit processes that improved code quality and security, leading to a 50% decrease in vulnerabilities detected and a 100% success rate in passing third-party security audits.

### Senior Blockchain Developer

Jungle Cats / June 2023 to July 2023

- Designed and developed Jungle Cat NFT that is used in the company's new blockchain ecosystem.
- Developed smart contracts integrating Jungle Cat NFT on Solana Blockchain System with high quality, speed and security.
- Conducted thorough code reviews and provided technical guidance to junior developers on best practices for blockchain development, enhancing team efficiency and effectiveness.

## Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Honey Finance / December 2022 to June 2023

- Developed Smart Contracts working on Hivemapper Network based on Solana Blockchain System, which directly contributed to a 30% growth in security.
- Contributed to the design and architecture of decentralized applications (dApps) utilizing blockchain technology.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and implement end-to-end
- blockchain solutions for various industries. • Created RESTful APIs for seamless integration of blockchain applications with
- front-end interfaces. • Developed Front-end side that users can send NFT buying, selling and exchanging request to blockchain system, using Web3.js, Next.js, with userfriendly attitude.

## Senior Blockchain Develoer

Ratio Finance / September 2022 to December 2022

- Researched, installed, and debugged an smart contract system reducing transaction times and failures.
- Designed and implemented smart contracts using Rust on the Solana blockchain to automate key processes for a supply chain management company, reducing operational costs by 15%.
- Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and Web3.js.

# Junior Blockchain Develoer

Molana. Pte. Ltd / July 2022 to September 2022

- Worked collaboratively with cross-functional teams to integrate blockchain technology into existing systems · Developed Smart Contracts integrating Molana into blockchain ecosystem for
- swaping with other cryptocurrency, staking and farming.
- Contributed to the popularity of Molana cryptocurrency over people, improved crypto's secure, system speed and business

# Junior Blockchain Develoer

Hawksight / September 2021 to June 2022

- Collaborated with the team to draw up a new system design that improved blockchain scalability. • Developed and implemented smart contracts using Rust on the Solana
- blockchain platform.

# SKILLS

## Blockchain

Anchor Web3.js Solana ) Ethereum (Hardhat) (Truffle) Smart Contract ) Ethers.js

Cryptocurrency

### Web

React Angular Vue Svelte node.js socket.io bootstrap Material-UI jQuery

#### Operating System:

MS-DOS Windows Linux

**Others** 

Project Management

HR Management Cryptotgraphy Security

#### Programming Language



## PERSONALITY

- Problem-Solving
- Self-Motivated
- Hard-Working

## **EDUCATION**

- Jacksonville University 2016~2020
- · A. Philip Randolph Academies 2014~2016

## LANGUAGES

# **English**

Native Writer/Speaker/Listener